hardwarestore.com 2013-08-06

# Aubuchon Hardware Privacy Policy

Aubuchon Hardware is committed to protecting your privacy online. This policy explains how we collect, use, and safeguard your personal information. If you have any questions, please call toll-free **800-282-4393** or email us at [help@aubuchon.com](mailto:help@aubuchon.com). 

* * *

**What Information Do We Collect & How is it Used? **  
_Ordering Information_ \- When placing an order we ask for your name, mailing address, email address, and credit card information. This information is used to process and fulfill your order, send you a receipt, and inform you of your order status. 

_Contests and Give Aways_ \- When entering a contest or give away, we may ask for your name, email address, mailing address, and/or broad demographic information (age,gender,etc.). This information is used to administer the contest and/or notify winners. Demographic information is used to improve and focus the services and features offered to our customers. 

_Mailing List_ \- When signing up for the Aubuchon Hardware mailing list, we ask for your name, email address and ZIP code. This information is used to send you the requested email. You may unsubscribe at any time. 

_Site Usage Statistics_ \- We collect general site usage statistics to administer the site, determine shopping trends, and improve the overall shopping experience at HardwareStore.com. This data is not linked to personal identifiable information. 

* * *

**How We Protect Your Information**  
We maintain both electronic and procedural safeguards to ensure the maximum security of your personal information. All orders placed on our site are protected by the highest level of encryption and cannot be viewed or altered as information travels to our secure server. Once we receive your information, we store it on a secure server that is not accessible from the Internet. 

* * *

**Who Has Access To Your Information**  
Credit card transactions are processed by a trusted third-party financial institution. They receive only enough credit card and billing information to determine the validity of the card and process the transaction. 

Aubuchon Hardware does not sell or share names, credit card, or any personal information with any other third party. 

Additionally, we restrict access to stored personal information to only those employees who have a specific business need for utilizing it. 

* * *

**Use of Email**  
We occasionally email our customers with information about upcoming promotions, sales, new products, recipes, and exclusive special offers. 

If, for any reason, you do not wish to receive this information, simply follow the instructions in each email or contact us at [help@aubuchon.com](mailto:help@aubuchon.com). 

Please also remember that email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure method of transmitting sensitive information such as your credit card number. 

* * *

**Use of Cookies**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our site uses cookies to keep track of items, speed navigation, and determine which areas of the site are popular or unpopular. We may also use cookies to tailor site content to your interests based on your previous shopping preferences at HardwareStore.com. The information stored in this cookie does not directly contain any personally identifiable information. 

Be default, your browser is initially configured to accept cookies. Although not recommended, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. If you do this, you will need to call us at 800-282-4393 in order to place orders for products on HardwareStore.com.

* * *

**Privacy of Children**  
Aubuchon Hardware does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. We sincerely hope that all parents monitor their children's use of the Internet and make them aware of the concerns regarding the use of personal information online.

* * *

_Aubuchon Hardware is constantly improving the services provided to our customers. If new features affect this policy, we will post the changes on this page immediately. We urge you to review this page regularly so that you are always aware of our current privacy policy._

* * *

**Back to Top**
